e2bn.org 2010-05-11

# Privacy Statement - E2BN

### Privacy Statement

**Copyright**  
All website design, text, graphics, their selection and arrangement, and all software are Copyright © 2008, The East of England Broadband Network. All rights reserved. 

Permission is granted to copy electronically and to print in hard copy portions of this website for the purpose of:

Promoting E2BN and E2BN Services and Learning Resources. 

  **Privacy Statement**  
E2BN guarantees that any personally identifiable information, such as email addresses, gathered from this website (with urls beginning http://www.e2bn.org/) will not be sold, rented, loaned, or given to others. Your personal information is safe with E2BN.   
**  
Forms on this website**  
There are forms on this site which require the respondent to provide personally identifiable information. E2BN may use this information to send the respondent information about our website or promotional material. Respondents may opt-out of receiving such mailings by checking the box on the forms.   
**  
Web server logs and traffic analysis**  
E2BN collects data regarding visitors to the website. The domain name and IP address do not reveal personally identifiable information about the visitor other than the IP address from which they have accessed our site. E2BN uses this information to gather statistics from our traffic, but does not collect and evaluate this information for others.  
E2BN web servers do not record personally identifiable information about the visitor. This information is used only to initiate future improvements to the site. 

**Contacting us**  
E2BN may also use your contact information to let you know about enhancements to its site and/or services. If you would rather not receive this information please inform us.   
**  
Links to other sites**  
This site contains links to other sites. E2BN is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of external websites. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy. 

**Your use of www.e2bn.org**  
By using this website, you agree to the above policy. Any changes to this policy will be published here for your reference.
